VISHAL PARMAR

Market Research Analyst

**** +918460302974 **Vadodara**, Gujarat @ Vishal.4215@gmail.com

Website/Link

SUMMARY

With a diverse background in accounting. data analysis. and market research management across multiple organizations, I bring strong skills in leadership, communication, and problem-solving. As a former team member at Nielseniq in market research field, I exhibited traits of being detail-oriented driven by deadlines, and possessing a creative mindset

EDUCATION

06/2011

Bachelor Of Arts, Economics, 06/2011

Maharaja sayajirao University - Vadodara

EXPERIENCE

04/2019 - 03/2022 •

Vadodara

Title **Nielsenia**

Company Description

- · Managed weekly promotions for FMCG products in the Canadian market as a Reference Data Specialist at Nielseniq(BAND 8)
- · Consistently delivered high-quality data to clients on a weekly basis, leading to our team winning the conqueror the Odds award

10/2016 - 08/2018

Data Analyst

Location

REVOKARMAHUB PVT LTD

Company Description

- · Improved website visibility and search engine ranking through various optimisation techniques as a Data Analyst(SEO)
- Conducted keyword research, developed and implemented SEO strategies, analysed website performance and monitored search engine algorithm

02/2012 - 05/2016

Site Supervisor

Location

Shilpi Engineering Pvt Ltd

Company Description

- · Managed and coordinated all on-site activities during a shutdown or turnaround project at various refineries in India as a Site Supervisor
- · Oversaw a team of workers, ensured compliance with safety regulations, and ensured that the project gets completed on time while also liaising with project managers, contractors, and clients to ensure effective communication and coordination.

TECH SKILLS

Microsoft access

TECH SKILLS

- **Attention to details**
- Multi tasking
- **Consume insights**

Strong analytical and problem

Data collect and Data Analysis

Project management

Flexibility and adaptability

LANGUAGES

English Proficient Hindi Native





Gujarati Native

